Subhan Allah. Wa Alhamdu Lillah. Wa La Elaha Ella Allah.
Allahu Akbar Allahu Akbar Allahu Akbar Allahu Akbar
La Elaha Ella Allah La Elaha Ella Allah
La Elaha Ella Allah
There's an extra La Elaha Ella Allah.
Alhamdu Lillah. We praise God.
Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
And we bear witness that there is no god except the One God.
I think I have to explain this first. This is a gift from Naghmeh. And she got the biggest size they have. Extra large. She thinks I'm fat.
So, may God bless her and send her a wonderful husband, IN SHAA ALLAH.
She and Apamea are inseparable. Edip is having rough time.
Today is really a fantastic day because we are going to share together God's gift to us as a result of the
conference. As you know, God always gives us a gift every time we do something which is actually
a gift from God. The conference itself is a gift from God but each one of us underwent efforts
and financial sacrifices and time sacrifices. And where God sends... God is so generous. So, He sent us a gift
that is two great miracles. Each one of them makes the parting of the Red Sea a tiny miracle.
They're all God's miracles, the parting of the Red Sea, the miracles of Jesus and all the miracles we... we see
in the Quran are all God's miracles, but this miracle God specializes... I mean, honors especially by
calling it one of the great miracles with a... with a very strong assurance in the Arabic language
(74:35) إِنَّهَا لَإِحْدَى ٱلْكُبَرِ
إِنَّهَا إِحْدَى ٱلْكُبَرِ
is one of the great miracles but
(74:35) إِنَّهَا لَإِحْدَى ٱلْكُبَرِ
it is indeed, most assuredly, one of the great miracles. And this is in SURA, as you know it has to do
it is based on the number 19. I would ask you to situate yourself where you can see this.
It is in SURA 74, verse 35. It is one of the greatest miracles 7 plus 4 is
11 plus 3 is 14, plus 5 is 19. This adds up to 19. And we're going
to witness this together in addition to this miracle that you see on the wall.
And before I start explaining this, hopefully, make it clear to you,
I want to share with you how God collectively inspires the believers because in this miracle
on the wall here, we have the first Sura in the Quran consists of 7 verses, as
you know. And then, we wrote the number of every verse in the Quran. This is... these are the verses
in the first SURA. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. So, this represents the first Sura. It consists of 7
verses and these are the verses in it. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. The next Sura consists of
286 verses. So, you write this next to this number and then the number of every
verse in the Sura. 1 2 and so on to 286. This will represent Sura number 2. Now, you're putting
putting all these numbers next to each other until you go to the end of the Quran and... and
you end up with the number of digits each one of these is a digit. The number of digits is
12,692 which is a multiple of 19. This is the number of digits in this long number.
And the long itself is a multiple 19. OK. So, we know about this miracle on the wall.
Everyone who walks in this masjid can witness a perpetual miracle that anyone can witness
anywhere in the world. Now, the collective inspiration of the believers is that you
know, you met Ali Fazeli from New Mexico. Dr. Fazeli, a physicist who I was talking to...to
Abdullah and to a number of us and he said. OK. This is the first Sura. It has 7 verses. This is
the first verse. Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem (1:1). This is the second verse. Al hamdu Lillahi Rabbil ‘Alameen (1:2)
This is the third verse and so on. Then, the next Sura is 286 and this is the first verse says
ALIF LAM MEEM (2:1) So, what happened to Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem? It is not... it is not being
considered here. So, Ali said why don't you put a zero for Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem? Put a zero here.
And this is the first miracle we're going to witness today cause Abdullah went to his computer
and he put zero for every Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem. As you know, the first Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem
the first verse, number 1, has a number. So, there is no zero in the first Sura and Sura 9 does
not have Bism Allah. So, it will not have a zero. So, when you come to Sura 9, it will look like this.
This is now Sura 9. You put the number of the Sura and there you don't put a zero. You start with
the verse 1 right away. 1 2 3 and so on. With the other Suras, you put the number of
verses. You put the number of the Sura followed by the zero.
Edip: Instead of 9, it must be total number
of verses. It's not checking on.
You put the number of the Sura. You put the total number of
verses. Yes. So, you put...you put also the number of the Sura here because the disbelievers say why do
you ignore the number of the SURA? Anyway, with this miracle, anything that the disbelievers want
God gave them. He left no excuse for them. But the idea here is that we... Ali suggested the
zeros and sure enough when we put the zeros in for Bism Allah, the end result was a multiple 19.
Now, these colors are supposed to be erased easily.
So, let's take a number that represents Sura number 1
and the beginning of Sura number 2. Sura number 1 has... is number 1. It has 7 verses. Then,
you put the numbers of verses. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 and then you put Sura number
2. It has 286 verses. Then, the Bism Allah has a 0 and then 1 2 and so on to the end of the Sura.
And you go like this to the end of the Quran. Now, these zeros... they're not zeros because they are
in the middle of the number. You have 11. If you have 11, it's 11, right? You put a 0
in the middle of the number, it becomes 101. There is no connection mathematically between 11
and 101. So, these zeros were inserted in that big number and the end result is a very
long number that is 13,038 digits and is divisible by 19.
A woman: And the digits are divisible by 19?
The messenger: No.
The number of digits is not divisible by 19.
OK. This will take us to the second miracle which is even greater than this
one if you can believe that. So, let us all collectively fall prostrate before God.
I would lead you in the prostration and then we'll make... we'll repent to God and ask Him to guide us.
Tooboo Ela Allah.
Allahu Akbar
Alhamdu Lillah. We praise God.
Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
And we bear witness that there is no other god besides God.
These miracles that we're witnessing are mathematical... strictly mathematical or structural
miracles. They have nothing to do with the literary miracle in the Quran. As you know,
there is a literary miracle that has to do with the distribution of every letter. This
is... you know... you know the the Quranic initials. ALIF LAM MEEM at the beginning of SURA number
2. The counts of ALIF and LAM and MEEM are mathematically controlled. The counts of HA MEEM
in the seven HA MEEM-initialed Suras are mathematically controlled. Every letter in the Quran
is mathematically controlled. I'm talking about letters. Also, words are mathematically controlled
in the Quran. We're talking about the literary mathematical composition. The word God, as you
know, there's 2698 times in the Quran. And if you add the numbers
of verses wherever the word God is mentioned, there's 118,123 which is also a multiple 19.
The word Quran happens in the Quran 57
times. 19 times 3. When you add the Suras and verses wherever the word Quran is
found, the total is 44008. 4408.
4408 which is also a multiple 19. So, we're talking about a giant
Rubik's Cube which is consisting of literary... two sections: a literary mathematical composition
where the letters and the words are mathematically composed and distributed far beyond human ability.
In Sura 17, verse 81, it says if all the humans and all the jinns banded together to produce
a Quran like this, they cannot do. And it has nothing to do with literature. It has to do with this
this impossible mathematical composition which is very simple to understand but very impossible
to imitate. What we're talking about today is strictly mathematical numbers. You take any book
from the library. Every book in the library has chapters and sentences and take those chapters
and number the sentences and see if there's any mathematical pattern in them. You will not find any.
If you find anything, it will be by coincidence and maybe one, one chance of some some kind
of of the... like... for example the number of sentences may be divisible by the number of
chapters by accident in one of the books. But that that would be the extent of it. So, we're talking now
by strictly mathematics. It has nothing to do with the literary sense. The second miracle that we are witnessing.
Let us take the Quran from the first verse to the last verse and give these verses numbers that
Abdullah called a sequential number. So, Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem (1:1). We have so number 1.
Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem is the first verse.
Al hamdu Lillahi Rabbil ‘Alameen (1:2)
Arrahman Arraheem (1:3)
Maliki Yawm Eddeen (1:4)
Eyyaka Na’abudu Wa Eyyaka Nasta’aeen (1:5)
Ehdina Al-Serata Al-Mustaqeem (1:6)
Serata Al-Lazeena An’amta ‘Alayhim Ghayri Al-Maghdoobi ‘Alayhim Wa Laddaalleen (1:7)
These are the first 7 verses of the Quran. And then we go to Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem of the second Sura.
This'll be number 8 and then the first verse of Sura number 2 says ALIF LAM MEEM. That will be number 9.
Are you following me? So, we'll keep going to the end of the Quran. The last verse is number 6346
which is a multiple of 19. This is the... all the verses of the Quran including
Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem in every Sura. Sura 9 does not have any Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem. OK.
Now, of course, this is verse number 1. This is number 2. This is number 3. This is number 4.
This is number 5 6 7 0 because this is the first Bism Allah of Sura number 2 and this
is verse number 1 of Sura number 2. And this is verse 6 of the last Sura of the Quran. So, here
we have two sets of numbers. We have the number of the verse and it's sequential number in the Quran.
So, the last verse in the Quran is number 6 of the last Sura. It is verse number 6. But
it is number 6346 in the whole Quran. Is this simple? Everybody's following this. This is very easy.
So, what Abdullah did; he put all these numbers next to each other to form one very long number
but he also put the number of the Sura before every Sura. So, before the numbers of Sura number 1,
he put... the number of the Sura which is 1. So, now the number representing the first Sura of
the Quran will be 1 1 1 2 2 3 3 4 4 5 5 6 6 7 7 and then we put Sura number 2
and then 0 8 1 9 2 10 3 11 4 12... are you following me? No. OK. The first
the first Sura in the Quran is 7 verses. And they are verses number 1 2 3 4 5 6 7.
If you... when you arrange them from the beginning of the Quran sequentially, they are also
number 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 and then the Bism Allah of Sura number 2 is number 8. The
first verse in Sura number 2 is number 9. So, what we're doing in this column here
we're just giving a number to every verse of the Quran from the beginning to the end. So, if you
go to the middle of the Quran, for example, verse number 1 of the last Sura in the Quran. When you count
from the beginning of the Quran, it becomes number 6341. 6341. In other words, up to
the first verse of the last Sura, we have 6341 verses. When
you go to the last verse of the Quran, it is verse number 6 in the last Sura.
(114:6) مِنَ ٱلْجِنَّةِ وَٱلنَّاسِ
This number 6 here says the last verse of Sura number 114 and it is number
6346 from the beginning of the Quran. It is number 6 from the beginning
of the Sura. It is number 6346 from the beginning of the Quran. OK. So far... so far so good?
So, Abdullah put the number of every verse and the number of this verse from the beginning of the Quran.
So, verse number 7 in Sura Al-Fãtehah, Sura Al-Hamd is verse number 7 and it
is also the 7th verse from the beginning of the Quran. And then Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem
of Sura number 2 is number 0, as you know and it is the 8th verse from the beginning of
the Quran. The first verse in Sura number 2 is the 9th verse from the beginning of the Quran. So, these
numbers we put next to each other to form one big number, except the number of every Sura was at
the beginning of every Sura. So, this is Sura number 1. The number representing Sura
number 1 would be...here it is... will be Sura number 1, verse number 1 in the Sura. It is verse number
1 in the whole Quran and then verse number 2 is also number 2 from the beginning of the Quran.
3. This was also 3. 4... this all one number. 4 4 5 5 6 6 7 7. Then, we go
to Sura number 2. We continue the numbers. It is Sura number 2 and we have the Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem is number 0.
And it is the 8th verse. See? This one is the 7th verse. The 8th verse from the beginning of the Quran and then
verse number 1 of SURA number 2 which is the 9th verse from the beginning of the Quran. And
then verse number 2 is the 10th verse from the Quran and so on to the end of the Quran. We end up...
Now, I want you to observe this with me. This number of the Sura is one number. The number of the other verse is
another number and so on. Now, we come here to the double numbers. The second verse of SURA number
2 is number 2 but from the beginning of the Quran, it is number 10. So, this is a number and
this is a number. If you count the numbers in the long number, they are... there... they are... let me see...
12,806. 12806 numbers. This is a multiple 19. This is the
number of numbers. See, this is one number. It's 10 and this here also is one number. This is the last
verse in the Quran. This is verse number 6346 in the whole Quran. It is verse number 6 in the
last Sura. So, this is a number. This is a number. This is a number. The number of these numbers is
12806 which is a multiple of 19. Now, if you count the digits meaning there are 2 digits here. This
is 10, has 2 digits. These are 4 digits: 1 2 3 4. 4 digits. It is one number, but 4 digits.
When you count the digits in this long number, you have 3 7... Excuse me... 37088. This
is the number. This is one long number that has... has 37,088
digits in it. This number of digits is a multiple of 19 and the long number itself is also multiple of 19.
Allahu Akbar Subhan Allah
The whole world should be Muslim tomorrow. So. Is this... I mean, maybe this clarifies it.
Yes. This adds... this adds up to 19 and it is a multiple of 19. This is the total number of verses in the Quran. It is 19 times 334.
The number of digits in that number, the basic number which has the number of verses followed by the number of every verse.
This sheet of paper on the wall has the number of every verse in the whole Quran.
And the number of digits there is exactly twice as much as the number of
verses in the Quran. There is no... it's not necessary to have that
connection, but it is true. Now I don't wanna confuse you anymore. But is there anything else you can think of Abdullah
you need to point out?
Abdullah went to the computer to put the zeros in there and then he walks out with this
piece of paper, casually. I said Oh oh, Abdullah, you have a piece of paper in your hand. All I said was we want to start a new translation
of the Quran to be ready in case the demand increases and we have to print some more, maybe a few Millions
IN SHAA ALLAH. At the minute, the suggestion of the new translation came, the flood was beginning already.
It's just awesome. I don't know what... there's something I need to say but I forget what it is.
This really leaves us speechless. Is there anything that is mysterious to anybody who'd be embarrassed to... if you
wanna clarify any point. Otherwise, we will do the prayer and as we prostrate to God, we remember
these miracles. Oh, this is what I wanna say... as you know, SURA 9 had these 2
false verses and if we include these 2 false verses 128 and 129 in that number,
you don't have anything. You don't have it divisible by 19. The whole thing collapses and here we're
adding the zeros inside for Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheems. We're putting in zeros for each one
and you still have a divisible... If you include the 2 false verses, the whole thing
collapses. You have nothing. So, right now, we have something to talk about, something awesome.
When we inject these zeros... Where is it? This is a zero. Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem of Sura number 2.
When you come to Sura 9, there's no Bism Allah. If you put the zero, this...
this is worth erasing...here we're struggling with these
numbers. Hey, they are being erased. I just want to demonstrate for you Sura number 9.
OK. Open your eyes, now. The number where we inject the zeros
which is the first miracle we talked about. We put the Sura number. 9.
And then we put the first verse in it which is number 1.
Put the verse numbers? 127?
Abdullah: The previous miracle? Yeah. You put the one under... First one you put 100
The messenger: Yes. 127, right?
We put the verse numbers. This is the total number of verses in the Sura. If you put 129 which includes the two false
verses, of course, the whole thing collapses. And then you put verse number 1 2, and we go on to 127
and this will represent Sura number 9 and then after that we get to Sura number 10. We put
the number of the Sura right after that and then you put the number of verses which is, what, 106
for Sura number 10 and then you put Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem. a zero and then the first verse
and then the second verse and so on to 106. Now, Sura number 10, the number of verses and Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem
has a zero. Sura number 9 does not have Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem, so there is no zero. If
and at the end, the end result is a very long number that is a multiple of 19. If you
put Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem in Sura 9 and you put a zero here the whole thing collapses.